# **JOSE TOMMASO**

#### **PROFILE**

I consider myself a nice, friendly person, very easy to work with, honest, punctual and good team worker. Having worked in IT made me very interested in front-end web developing. I'm looking forward to continuing my career in this exciting field.

#### **SKILLS**

English - B2 Spanish - Native Team-Working Organizational skills Attention to quality

IT skills Analysing

Facility to learn new knowledge

#### CONTACT



+447426721843



tommaso\_j@hotmail.com

#### **ADDRESS**

Flat 5 The Centrum, Goodhind St. Judes BS5 0SN Bristol (United Kingdom)

#### **EXPERIENCE**



Feb 2016 - 27 Jun 2017

Warehouse Operative / Vitcas LTD, Bristol (UK) / www.vitcas.com DUTIES:

Manufacturing a range of products against fire.

Packing / Dispatching orders



Apr 2015 - Nov 2015

Warehouse Packer / Costumes R Us, Bristol (UK) / www.costumerusuk.com/ DUTIES:

Picking Orders from different locations within the warehouse.

Pack all the orders in boxes/bags.



Apr 2008 - Apr 2015

Insurance Agent / MAPFRE, Maracay (Venezuela) / www.mapfre.com.ve

## DUTIES:

Calculate premiums and establish payment method.

Customer service

Submit forms to customers.

Develop marketing strategies to compete with other individuals or companies who sell insurance.



Freelance IT Support 2008-2016

Resolve various service issues, including troubleshooting and repairing network connectivity issues, hardware and software problems.

Built and upgraded computers to best serve customer needs.

### **EDUCATION**



July 2017 - Present UDACITY.COM

Front-End Web Developer Nanodegree Program



March 2017 - July 2017 UDACITY.COM

Intro to Programming Nanodegree Program



2008 - 2011 Insurance Agent Training MAPFRE (VENEZUELA)



2001 - 2007 EDUCATIONAL UNIT COLLEGE "Calicantina"/U.E. Colegio Calicantina Secondary Science Education (VENEZUELA)